That it has happened
Om Om
[Music]
Hello friends, a very warm welcome to
all of you on my YouTube channel. We are your
Health and Life Insurance Consultant Kajal.
Hello friends, have you ever thought about
what will happen to your family after your death? How will
your children's lifestyle education and their
marriage be arranged for your semen? Have
you ever thought about how much money will you take with you to your wife?
Friends, today in this video
I will give you answers to all these questions. I will
tell you
where to invest and
where not to invest to secure your family. That too by taking examples of those people
who have already invested.
Now, those people who have
invested wisely, their families are
living a peaceful life and those who have taken
decisions out of greed, their
families are living their lives dependent on others.
Tomorrow,
due to some wrong investment made by you, your family may be left wandering from
door to door after you are gone.
Therefore,
make a guaranteed income plan for your family right now so that your
family can live a peaceful life even after you are gone. So, let's
start today.  There is a
video of how to buy it at a
price of Rs. Suppose there are three
friends Suraj, Deepak and Aman, they all
studied in the same college, all three are engineers and
work in the same company, after that they got
married, after that they had children too,
now after that Vindu took a statement, bought a
car on a loan of 42 lakhs, but the
age of these three is 8 lakhs, fact is this year, now Suraj,
Deepak and Ravan decided that we
will invest Rs.10000 per month, both have
two children, have a house loan of 42 lakhs
and have taken loan of 8 lakhs, now
they have to invest Rs.10000, Suraj
said that Muzaffar has invested all the money and
Suraj has invested Rs.10000 in the policy only,
Deepak said no I will
take a life insurance policy whose premium
will be Rs.500 per month, so that the
debt of Rs.50 lakhs on me will be covered,
I will invest the remaining money only at Rs.9500
and Aman said I will get a
loan of Rs.1 crore, whose premium will be Rs.  Just
₹14,100 per month so that I can buy my house,
my children's education, their lifestyle,
their marriage, my wife's pension,
I will secure all this, I will
invest the remaining 8600 rupees only. Now
they accepted that they had a 10% interest rate,
after just 5 years their money started increasing
and this money kept increasing for 1015-2025 years, you
can see from your birth chart how much money
they have got
and at the time of retirement when they turned 10 years old,
Suraj got Rs 1 crore 32 lakh,
Deepak got Rs 12500000 and Aman got
Rs 1 crore 13 lakh, after this they are living
their life very comfortably because
they got this money after their retirement,
but friends does this happen with every person, does
every person retire,
friends now they take another situation,
Suraj, Deepak, Kauda, ​​Vansh, these three were
going in a car and they met with a car accident in
which both of them died,
I am in Surat now, Suraj died at the age of 45, whatever
money he got  He had
invested only in a unit. He
got Rs 20 lakh 50 thousand of it but he
left a question for his wife as to
how the children would get married. Just think
why this happened. This happened
because Suraj
was in a state of intoxication that nothing would happen to him
but he met with an accident due to which his
family is now on the road. You can see for yourself.
Now let's see what happened with Deepak.
Deepak had taken a policy of Rs 50 lakhs, with which
his car and house expenses were met but what about the
children's education, what about the children's marriage, what about the
wife's pension, what would happen to the
family after his death.
He did not think about the family at all. That is why like Suraj,
Deepak's family is also on the road. Now let's
talk about the mind which said that even if the
returns are a little less, it does not
matter but my family should be safe.
His family got Rs 17 lakh 68 thousand
but he also got Rs 1.5 crore. With
that Rs 1.5 crore, his wife has done
everything for the children's education, lifestyle and lifestyle.
Like Suraj and Deepak, we have not taken any wrong
investment. Aman has taken
life insurance keeping his family in mind.  He
took a policy and today his family is
living a good and happy life even though it is in his name. His
family is completely safe. Now
tell me in the comments, whose planning among the three friends did
you like the most.
Whenever we go to the market and buy the best things from the best shops,
we only listen to the best products,
so ca
n't we buy the best wisdom for our family?
Friends, a life insurance policy is the
best Mastani. We should sit at home and
think about our exercise and like it is. If something happens to you, will
my wife be able to hide all my liabilities,
hide all my worries, will she be able to
run the family with money? Will she be able to pay for the children's
education, marriage, retirement and loans?
Friends, we must do this with animals.
If all this is not done after you are gone, then only you will be
responsible for it. Only you
and your friends. If you do
not want to be responsible for these things, then contact me using the
WhatsApp number you are seeing on this screen
and keep your
family safe. We do not want
your family to
depend on others after you are gone. We
think about the future of your family.
All the benefits of the life insurance policy will be for
you and your children.  If this is
happening to you then please pay attention to this matter. So
friends, I hope that in today's video,
you will
definitely take a life insurance policy, not for yourself
but for your family
because there is no one in this world greater than our family.
Friends, if you
found this video of mine famous, then please subscribe to my channel,
please like the video
and press the like button so that
you keep getting the latest updates of my videos. With regards to this,
thank you very much for staying in this video for years. Thank you for
watching our video.